<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Djinn List</string>

    <string name="view_djinni_caught">Obtained?</string>

    <!-- Golden Sun Djinns -->
    <string name="golden_sun_name_1">Flint</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_1">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_1">Strike a blow that can cleave stone</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_1">World Map, South of Vale</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_1">It is automatically acquired once you leave vale and enter the
    overworld for the first time, where a cutscene has Flint talk to you and give a tutorial on how to use Djinn. It will join you
    no matter how many times you attempt to refuse it joining you, but its various responses may be amusing.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_1">When Flint is used in battle, the user strongly attacks a target with a Venus-based attack
    equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack increased by 60%.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_1">When set, Flint increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base PP by 4, and base Attack by 3.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_2">Forge</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_2">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_2">Boost party attack with flame\'s fury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_2">Goma Cave</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_2">Forge resides in Goma Cave, on an elevated ledge near a person bystanding on the
    ground level. An earth pillar near the bystander and the Djinni must be pushed right, then up onto the circular indentation in the
    ground where the pillar will stay permanently. Then the party continues to go through the dungeon, and will eventually make it to
    the elevated portion of the area where they can hop across the earth pillar and initiate the battle with Forge.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_2">When Forge is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts get buffed with a
    25% temporary increase to their respective attack ratings.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_2">When set, Forge increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base Attack by 2, base Agility by 2,
    and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_3">Gust</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_3">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_3">Attack with mighty wind gusts</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_3">Bilibin</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_3">Gust is located in a cavern underneath the town of Bilibin. The gold statue of
    Lady McCoy in the center of the town conceals an entrance into the area, and can be moved aside so the entrance can be accessed;
    players will find out that though they can see Gust off to the right of the screen, they cannot reach it because of the placement
    of another gold statue against a wall. The actual method of getting to Gust is to go up the stairs to the right of the statue outside,
    and walk down until you\'re walking on top of the town\'s wooden gate permiter clockwise. A cave entrance at the west end of the town
    leads to the same underground cave, but now you stand just to the left of the gold statue. Cast Move to move the statue one space down,
    and now you can hop right to where Gust awaits.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_3">When Gust is used in battle, the user attacks a target with a Jupiter-based attack equal in
    power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an aditional 10 damage points added to the result. There is then a chance that all of the
    resulting damage will be doubled, signified by a second strike to the attack visually.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_3">When set, Gust increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Attack by 2, and base Agility by 2.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_4">Granite</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_4">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_4">Create a mighty earthen barrier</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_4">Kolima</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_4">Granite is visible in the town of Kolima, fenced in a small enclosure next to one of the
    tree-houses, and you cannot reach it from the outside. To reach it, go behind the tree-house and walk down, so that you enter a secret
    back door into a small room. Following the ladder and the resultant underground cave trail (complete with random battles) leads you into the
    enclosed area with the Djinnim ready for grabbing.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_4">When Granite is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts are buffed for until the end
    of the turn with a protective effect that decreases all damage done to them from enemy attacks by 50%. This effect has the "strikes first"
    property, meaning it will be the first performed action in a given turn regardless of the agility rating of the user and any other unit
    in battle.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_4">When set, Granite increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Defense by 2, base Agility by 2, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_5">Breeze</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_5">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_5">Boost party resistance</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_5">Tret Tree</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_5">Breeze resides in the Tret Tree dungeon-style location, in the upper-rightmost corner
    of the large exterior screen comprising of tree branches to climb up through. It is obscured by the leafy aspect of the scenery that gets cleared
    away by the "aura vision" surrounding Isaac as he approaches, so to know it is there you would have to walk up to the end of the topmost
    branches and reveal it. It must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_5">When Breeze is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts are buffed with an additional
    40 resistance points to all their resistances.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_5">When set, Breeze increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12, base PP by 5, base Defense by 2, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_6">Fever</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_6">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_6">Wrap a foe in feverish delusion</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_6">Imil</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_6">Fever reposes in Imil Falls Cave, the tiny cavern at the town of Imil, reachable by sliding
    around through the frozen river and into the hole of the frozen waterfall. To reach there, first you have to stand in front of the snowman
    at the north end of the town and cast Move to shift it left and drop it onto the frozen river below. Then entering the river via the opening
    just to the right of the sanctum in the southwest part of town, slide right, up, left, up, left, up, right, up, left, up, right, and up
    to enter the opening. You automatically slide into Fever, and press A to immediately add it to your collection.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_6">When Fever is used in battle, the user attacks a target and an orange cloud is let loose upon impact,
    dealing a Mars-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 30 damage points added to the result. There
    is then a chance that the target will be afflicted by Delusion.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_6">When set, Fever increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base Attack by 3, and base Agility by 2.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_7">Fizz</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_7">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_7">Restore HP with calming water</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_7">Mercury Lighthouse</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_7">Fizz is a Djinni that is automatically handed to you as you play through the game, being
    present on Mia as soon as she joins your party in Mercury Lighthouse somewhat early on in Golden Sun. Aside from Flint, Fizz is the only Djinni
    in the game that is impossible not to obtain.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_7">When Fizz is used in battle, a targeted Adept on the player\'s side is cured by an amount equal to
    60% of their maximum HP.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_7">When set, Fizz increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base PP by 4, and base Defense by 3.</string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_8">Sleet</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_8">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_8">Drench a foe to drop its attack</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_8">Mercury Lighthouse</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_8">Sleet is located in a hidden room behind one of the many waterfall-walls in a hallway immediately following a room
    where a pipe spout pushes open a massive section of wall to the left to reveal a door; you must press up against the wall so that you enter
    the room as though you walked through a house\'s door. It must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_8">When Sleet is used in battle, an image of a Mercury Djinni projects a stream of icy shards at the target, dealing
    a Mercury-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 30 damage points added to the result. There is then a chance
    that the target\'s Attack rating will be temporarily reduced by 25%.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_8"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_9">Zephyr</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_9">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_9">Boost party Agility with a swift wind</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_9">Fuchin Falls Cave</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_9">Zephyr is located in the Fuchin Falls Cave dungeon, in a room with water that is crossed by
    rolling logs. It shouldn\'t be hard to figure out how to reach it, which is by rolling on the top horizontal log down, rolling the lower left
    vertical log one space left, rolling the horizontal log back up, hopping to the lower left vertical log, and rolling it right. Zephyr must
    be battled to be obtained.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_9">When Zephyr is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts get their Agility ratings
    temporarily buffed to +100%, the maximum agility bonus possible. It doubles everyone\'s speed, in other words.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_9"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_10">Quartz</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_10">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_10">Revive a downed ally</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_10">Mogall Forest</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_10">Quartz is located late in Mogall Forest. In a screen you enter down from the top end, to the
    right of the screen is a rock right below a horizontal log - position yourself above the log and use Move to move the rock down one space into the
    circular indenture in the ground, then push the log down. Push a second horizontal log down, push the vertical log from the right to left, and
    go down and left to reach the Djinni. It must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_10" formatted="false">When Quartz is used in battle, a targeted downed party member has a 50% chance to be revived, with
    their HP restored to 50% of their maximum HP meter.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_10"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_11">Mist</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_11">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_11">Lull a foe into deep sleep</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_11">Xian</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_11">Mist is visibly located in the town of Xian. To get to it, note a woman that patrols between the
    river and the right of two brown doors embedded into a brown wall below the town\'s dojo. As soon as you talk to her, a Frostable puddle appears
    beneath her, and she berates you for making her drop her bucket of water. Talk to her when there is one tile between herself and the door she stops
    in front of, and use Frost on the resultant puddle to form a pillar you can hop across to reach the Djinni to the right.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_11">When Mist is used in battle, the user deals an attack that lets loose a white vaporous cloud on impact,
    dealing a Mercury-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack, increased by 30%. The target may be afflicted with Sleep.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_11"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_12">Corona</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_12">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_12">Boost party defense with a heat aura</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_12">World Map, north of Xian</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_12">Corona is the first Djinni players can come across in Golden Sun that is randomly encountered in
    a specific area of the overworld that otherwise appears to be pointless scenery. Thus, it is almost always missed by players playing the game the
    first time without any outside information. The battle with Corona may ensue in place of a random battle at the end of a vertical stretch of land
    parallel to the Mogall Forest region in Angara, in the pictured "island" north of Xian, and Corona then, of course, must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_12" formatted="false">When Corona\'s battle effect is used, all currently active and alive Adepts get buffed
    with a 25% temporary increase to their respective defense ratings.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_12"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_13">Spritz</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_13">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_13">Restore party HP with soothing mist</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_13">Altin Peak</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_13">Spritz is located in a larger room in the lower portion of the multi-level Altin Peak dungeon.
    It is immediately visible as soon as you enter the room. To reach it, cast Frost on a puddle on ground level, and move the earth pillar to the left
    of that one space left, constructing a hoppable path to the elevated area containing a mine cart. Also interact with a switch so that the arrow
    pointing right points left. Hop into the mine cart and ride it twice in a row, and you will be dropped off to Spritz\' position.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_13" formatted="false">When Spritz is used in battle, all currently alive and battling Adepts have their HP
    restored by 30% of their respective maximum HP values.</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_13"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_14">Smog</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_14">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_14"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_14">Lamakan Desert</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_14"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_14"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_14"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_15">Vine</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_15">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_15"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_15">World Map, west of Lamakan Desert</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_15"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_15"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_15"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_16">Scorch</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_16">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_16"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_16">Kalay Tunnel</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_16"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_16"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_16"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_17">Sap</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_17">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_17"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_17">Vault</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_17"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_17"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_17"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_18">Kite</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_18">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_18"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_18">Vale Cave</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_18"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_18"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_18"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_19">Ember</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_19">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_19"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_19">Tolbi</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_19"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_19"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_19"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_20">Hail</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_20">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_20"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_20">World Map, south of Altmiller Cave</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_20"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_20"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_20"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_21">Ground</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_21">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_21"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_21">Kalay Docks</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_21"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_21"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_21"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_22">Squall</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_22">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_22"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_22">Altmiller Cave</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_22"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_22"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_22"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_23">Tonic</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_23">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_23"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_23">Lunpa Fortress</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_23"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_23"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_23"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_24">Flash</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_24">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_24"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_24">Suhalla Desert</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_24"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_24"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_24"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_25">Dew</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_25">Mercury</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_25"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_25">Suhalla Gate</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_25"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_25"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_25"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_26">Bane</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_26">Venus</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_26"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_26">Crossbone Isle (requires Lift)</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_26"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_26"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_26"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_27">Torch</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_27">Mars</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_27"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_27">Lalivero</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_27"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_27"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_27"></string>

    <string name="golden_sun_name_28">Luff</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_element_28">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_flavor_28"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_location_28">Babi\'s Lighthouse</string>
    <string name="golden_sun_catching_description_28"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_battle_effect_28"></string>
    <string name="golden_sun_set_bonus_28"></string>

    <!-- Lost Age Djinns -->
    <string name="lost_age_name_1">Echo</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_1">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_1">Attack with a double strike</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_1">World Map, South of Daila</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_1">It is automatically acquired once Felix\’s party leaves Daila and enters the
    overworld for the first time, and in a cutscene, Echo talks to him and gives a tutorial on using Djinn. It will join you no
    matter how many times you refuse to let it, but its amusing responses range from outright begging to promising that Felix will be
    “all kinds of strong” and that Echo “won\’t be a burden and eat all your chips or anything.”</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_1">When Echo is used in battle, the user attacks a target with a two-hit strike that propels
    the target into the air, dealing a Venus-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack, increased by 60%.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_1">When set, Echo increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base PP by 4, and base Attack by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_2">Fog</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_2">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_2">Blind an enemy wigh fog</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_2">Kandorean Temple</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_2">Fog is found in the Kandorean Temple, on an alcove reachable by casting the Lash
    Psynergy on a coiled rope. Lash is the reward at the end of the dungeon, however, acquired in a cutscene with Master Poi after
    coming out of an exit from the cave area back into the temple area. You would have to reenter the exit you came out of and
    backtrack to the Djinni once you have Lash, but it is certainly closer to the dungeon\'s exit than the entrance. After climbing
    up to Fog, you must battle it in order to attain it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_2">When Fog is used in battle, the user leaps forward to strike the target and let loose
    a vaporous blue cloud upon impact, dealing a Mercury-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with
    an additional 30 damage points. There is then a chance that the target will be afflicted with Delusion.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_2">When set, Fog increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Defense by 2, base Agility by 2, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_3">Breath</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_3">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_3">Restore HP quickly</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_3">Shrine of the Sea God</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_3">Breath is located in the Shrine of the Sea God, specifically the earlier portion
    explorable so long as you have the Lash Psynergy from Kandorean Temple. As soon as you use Lash on the coiled rope in the first
    room, a cutscene with the two young boys Riki and Tavi transpires in which they thank you and report that they were trying to
    catch the flying creature for themselves before the tidal wave struck. After they leave, you more or less chase Breath through
    some of the dungeon; one particularly important point to retain is that when you get to three stairwells in close proximity
    to each other, enter one of the two upper stairs and cross a bridge so that Breath is seen fleeing north from the floor below
    you, then return and take the lower stairs. You will then go up to where Breath is, but before attempting to catch it, press
    the lit-up torch against the empty section of wall, so that the Djinni will trap itself and you can battle it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_3" formatted="false">When Breath is used in battle, target ally Adept is healed by 40% of its maximum HP. This effect
    has the "strikes first" property that guarantees it to occur as the first action in a given turn regardless of the user\'s
    Agility, unless another move with the strikes-first property is used in the same turn, in which case Agility will be measured.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_3">When set, Breath increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Defense by 3, and base Agility by 4.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_4">Cannon</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_4">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_4">Strike with the power of Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_4">Dehkan Plateau</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_4">Cannon is somewhat infamous for being found in the Dehkan Plateau, but only
    actually acquirable after being chased through the entire location by the player and forcing you to solve puzzles it
    inadvertently creates for you as you proceed after it. Eventually, you corner it in a room where it can hop across two
    separate kinds of pillars if you approach it, but instead of doing that you should climb down and use your newly acquired
    Pound Psynergy to pound down the pillar to the left, then climb back up. Cannon can then be battled and acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_4">When Cannon is used in battle, the user charges forward to tackle the target while
    cloaked in a fiery aura, dealing a Mars-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an
    additional 40 damage points added to the result.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_4">When set, Cannon increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10 and base Attack by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_5">Iron</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_5">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_5">Bolster the party\'s defense</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_5">World Map, west of Madra</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_5">Iron is the first Djinni players can come across inThe Lost Age that is
    randomly encountered in a specific area of the overworld that otherwise appears to be featureless scenery. Compared to
    other Djinn found and fought like this, though, Iron is perhaps the only one that players without any form of outside
    help or guidance have a pretty good chance to stumble upon regardless; Iron is located in the green forest bordering the
    left of the town of Madra, so if a random battle occurs while you\'re crossing the forest on the way to Madra, you will
    most likely engage in the battle with Iron. Then, of course, it must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_5" formatted="false">When Iron is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts get buffed
    with a 25% temporary increase to their respective defense ratings.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_5">When set, Iron increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11, base Defense by 2, and base Agility by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_6">Sour</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_6">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_6">Reduce a foe\'s resistance</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_6">World Map, northeast of Mikasalla and south of Osenia Cavern</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_6">Sour is a Djinni that is randomly encountered in a specific area of the
    overworld that otherwise appears to be pointless scenery. Thus, it is very often missed by players playing the game the
    first time without any outside information. The battle with Sour may ensue in place of a random battle in the pictured
    area northeast of the town of Mikasalla and just below the cavern containing the Megaera summon tablet. It must be defeated
    to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_6" formatted="false">When Sour is used in battle, the user deals a Mercury-based
    attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack increased by 50%. There is then a chance that all of the
    target\'s resistances may be lowered by 40 each. Note that resist-dropping effects may be stacked to a maximum of -80.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_6">When set, Sour increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base PP by 4, and base Attack by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_7">Blitz</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_7">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_7">Numb a foe with a lightning strike</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_7">Yampi Desert</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_7">Blitz is located in Yampi Desert, on an elevated portion of desert that must
    be hopped onto using Poundable wooden pillars - you must pound the pillars that allow you to climb up to the elevated level
    of the screen without pounding any of the pillars you need to use to hop to where Blitz is. From where you enter the screen
    from the lower left, pound the immediately visible left pillar visible, go to the right in the area beyond that, pound the
    rightmost pillar there, and pound the right of the two topmost pillars that are up against the north wall. Climb up the
    resultant ladder, hop left, go down, hop right, go down, hop down once and left twice across the two concurrent wood pillars,
    go down and right, and hop right to reach Blitz\' area, where it must be battled to be obtained. Considering the hefty amount
    of work needed to get onto Blitz\' area, the importance of saving before the battle cannot be stressed enough.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_7">When Blitz is used in battle, the user strikes the target and a series of four
    lightning bolts circle around the target briefly after the strike transpires. The attack deals a Jupiter-based attack
    equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 30 damage points added to the result, and
    there is then a chance that the target will be afflicted with Stun.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_7">When set, Blitz increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base PP by 4, and base Attack by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_8">Spark</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_8">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_8">Revive an ally with cheers of support</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_8">Mikasalla, requires Scoop</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_8">Spark is located in the town of Mikasalla, in a separate screen north of the
    main town where it is visible just by walking up to the top. It is only reachable, however, with the Scoop Psynergy earned
    from a boss fight in Yampi Desert; go to the tiny ranch with the chicken and sheep in the lower left corner of the town, and
    cast Scoop in the exact center to open up a ladder, which leads to an underground cave trail. Following it leads you to the
    Djinni, which you can pick up without a fight.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_8" formatted="false">When Spark is used in battle, a targeted downed party member has
    a 60% chance to be revived with his or her HP restored to 60% of his or her maximum HP meter.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_8">When set, Spark increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11 and base PP by 6.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_9">Ether</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_9">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_9">Focus will restore PP</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_9">Garoh</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_9">Ether is available in the town of Garoh, automatically handed to you after two
    lengthy cutscenes. First, you will have to have completed the Air\'s Rock dugneon. Then, at Garoh, use the Reveal Psynergy you
    acquired there to enter the entrance you see the werewolf that says "What!? Outsiders, here?" exit and reenter. Follow your
    way and eventually trigger a cutscene with the werewolf, Maha. You automatically return to the town\'s inn, and the town is now
    under daylight. Enter the hidden entrance again and return to where you spoke with Maha to trigger another, lengthier cutscene
    with him. Maha will eventually produce the Jupiter Djinni for Felix\'s party to take on their travels (learning from the party
    in the process that the name "Djinni" is what you call creatures like this), and you automatically acquire it. In a sense,
    this is another eventual reward you get for completing Air\'s Rock.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_9" formatted="false">When Ether is used in battle, a targeted Adept\'s PP meter is
    restored by an amount equal to 30% of his or her maximum PP meter.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_9">When set, Ether increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base PP by 4, base Agility by 3, and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_10">Kindle</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_10">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_10">Increase all allies\' attack</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_10">Gondowan Cliffs</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_10">Kindle resides in Gondowan Cliffs. To easily find it in the mazelike location,
    when you get to the stretched-out tightrope you walk to cross the river below, climb up two vines to the right, then follow
    the path downward past a small puddle to Kindle\'s position. There, it must be battled to be obtained.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_10" formatted="false">When Kindle is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts
    get buffed with a 25% temporary increase to their respective attack ratings.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_10">When set, Kindle increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base Attack by 5, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_11">Chill</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_11">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_11">Strike to reduce a foe\'s defense</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_11">World Map, southwest of Naribwe</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_11">Chill is a Djinni that is randomly encountered in a specific area of the overworld
    that otherwise appears to be pointless scenery. Thus, it is very often missed by players playing the game the first time without
    any outside information. The battle with Chill may ensue in place of a random battle in the pictured area in the bottom part of the
    central forested stretch of land area south ofNaribwe, where it then must be defeated to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_11" formatted="false">When Chill is used in battle, the user strikes the enemy and a large,
    misty white cloud is let off to surround the target on impact, dealing a Mercury-based attack equal in power to the user\'s
    normal physical attack with an additional 40 damage points added to the result. There is then a chance that the target\'s
    Defense rating will be temporarily reduced by 25%.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_11">When set, Chill increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base PP by 3, and base Defense by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_12">Spring</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_12">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_12">Restore HP with healing herbs</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_12">Kibombo, comes with Piers</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_12">Spring is a Djinni that is automatically handed to you as you play through the
    game, being present on Piers as soon as he joins your party in the town of Kibombo somewhat early on in The Lost Age. Spring
    is one of three Djinn in The Lost Age - the others being Echo and another Mercury Djinni in Piers\' possession, Shade - that
    is impossible not to obtain.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_12" formatted="false">When Spring is used in battle, a targeted Adept on the player\'s
    side has their HP cured by an amount equal to 70% of their maximum HP.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_12">When set, Spring increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11 and base PP by 5.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_13">Shade</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_13">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_13">Create a watery shield</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_13">Kibombo, comes with Piers</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_13">Shade is a Djinni that is automatically handed to you as you play through
    the game, being present on Piers as soon as he joins your party in the town of Kibombo somewhat early on in The Lost Age.
    Shade is one of three Djinn in The Lost Age - the others being Echo and another Mercury Djinni in Piers\' possession,
    Spring - that is impossible not to obtain.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_13" formatted="false">When Shade is used in battle, all damage done to all current battling
    party members is reduced by 60% for the duration of that turn, and this effect is always cast first regardless of the user\’s
    Agility.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_13">When set, Spring increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Defense by 3, and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_14">Steel</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_14">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_14">Siphon a foe\'s HP with a kiss</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_14">Gabomba Statue</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_14">Steel is located in the Gabomba Statue. Players playing through on their
    first time or without a guide, however, may find this Djinni somewhat difficult to acquire as it may not be immediately
    obvious what to do. First of all, reverse all gears in the dungeon - this is necessary to complete the dungeon to begin
    with. Then in one of the upper floors, there are two pink gears side by side rotating downward into what would seem to
    be an abyss, which is what\'s pictured. Step behind the left gear and press down to jump onto it and fall down to the
    floor below; you will land very near Steel, where it can then be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_14" formatted="false">When Steel is used in battle, the user strikes the target
    and siphons a glowing yellow energy out of it, dealing a Venus-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal
    physical attack increased by 30%. The user\'s HP will be restored by an amount equal to 50% of the damage dealt to
    the target. If the target dies, the user\'s HP is restored by half of the target\'s health before the attack.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_14">When set, Steel increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Attack by 4, base Defense by 2, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_15">Waft</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_15">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_15">Calm a foe with soothing scents</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_15">Kibombo Mountains, requires Frost</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_15">Waft is located near the northwestern exit of Kibombo Mountains, but
    accessible only on your return trip back from Kibombo to the north when Piers has joined your party - only he can
    cast the Frost Psynergy needed to reach it. Climb up the first three sets of stairs, go down to Frost the puddle into
    an ice pillar, go up to climb up one more stairway, go right and down to hop across the ice pillar down and right, and cast Growth
    and climb up it to reach the Djinni. Waft must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_15" formatted="false">When Waft is used in battle, a holographic image of a Jupiter
    Djinni floats above the target and surrounds the target with a purple pillar of energy, dealing a Jupiter-based attack
    equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 40 damage points added to the result, and there is then a chance that the target will be afflicted with Sleep.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_15">When set, Waft increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11 and base Attack by 4.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_16">Char</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_16">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_16">Paralyze foes with a strong blow</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_16">Madra, requires the Healing Fungus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_16">Char is in the possession of a pair of residents living in the two-story
    residential house in Madra, visible in a fenced-in area on the second floor. To get it into your collection, though, you
    first have to have collected the Healing Fungus from the Gondowan Cliffs (this item is accessible by casting Frost on a
    puddle over there and using the resulting pillar as a hopping step). Then present the Healing Fungus to the old man, and a
    short cutscene will have them give it to you as a "pet" in exchange.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_16" formatted="false">When Char is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mars Djinni
    projects a red stream of grainy energy at the target, and the target is hit with red static electricity as it is buffeted.
    It deals a Mars-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 50 damage points added
    to the result. There is then a chance that the target will be afflicted by Stun.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_16">When set, Char increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Attack by 2, base Agility by 2, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_17">Mud</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_17">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_17">Slow a foe with sticky mud</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_17">Gabomba Catacombs</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_17">Mud is located in the Gabomba Catacombs. To reach it, in the first grass-covered
    room you climb down into, go up so that you\'re in the semi-enclosed area between rocks below the mass of grass just to the left
    of the elevated area you climb down from. Cast Cyclone here and you will automatically be transported through a "cyclone ground
    portal" hidden within the leaves above, and you will be dropped into the floor below right next to Mud\'s position. Save, then
    battle Mud to earn out.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_17" formatted="false">When Mud is used in battle, the user lobs mounds of orange mud at the
    positions of each member of the enemy party. All enemies\' agility ratings are temporarily lowered down to 50%, the lowest value
    the Agility rating can be debuffed down to. This is identical to the effect of the Venus Djinni Vine in The Lost Age.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_17">When set, Mud increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base PP by 4, and base Agility by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_18">Flower</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_18">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_18">Refresh allies and restore HP</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_18">Taopo Swamp</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_18">Flower is located in Taopo Swamp, and is pretty much the "main reward of interest"
    of the section of the swamp\'s caves it is located in (whereas a piece of Star Dust is the main reward of interest in the other
    main section of the caves). When you see it, it is standing unreachable at the edge of an abyss with an air spout on the cave wall
    above it. On either side of it is an earth pillar that can be pushed in front of an air spout. When both earth pillars are covering
    an air spout each, Flower will be blown off the edge and fall to the floor below. To properly follow it, slide down the second
    cliff slide to the right of Flower\'s position. It must be battled to be obtained, though definitely save before trying to get it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_18" formatted="false">When Flower\'s battle effect is used, all currently alive and battling
    Adepts have their HP restored by 30% of their respective maximum HP values.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_18">When set, Flower increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12 and base PP by 4.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_19">Meld</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_19">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_19">Launch a powerful team strike</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_19">Islet Cave</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_19">Meld is found in Islet Cave, in the immediately accessible portion of it as opposed
    to the later portion accessible only with the Teleport Psynergy at the end of the game. Getting to the optional dungeon to begin
    with is complex in and of itself, making Meld essentially the "main reward" for first reaching Islet Cave. In the right watery
    room with rolling logs, after you roll right, simply go down to the horizontal log below and roll it up to Meld\'s position at the
    top of the area. It must be battled.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_19" formatted="false">Meld\'s battle effect is unique: Visually, it appears as the user and
    one of the other currently active party members attacking a target together. The Adept that is chosen to be the "second attacker"
    alongside the user is the Adept with the highest Attack rating other than the user. The damage calculation is based mostly on the
    "second attacker"; it is the second attacker\'s attack that is used as the base for the damage, and it is the second attacker\'s
    Venus power rating that is applied for elemental resistance calculations. However, during the attack the second attacker\'s Attack
    rating is treated as though it has additional attack rating equal to 25% of the user\'s own attack rating (meaning that 25% of the
    Meld user\'s own attack rating is the only contribution to the attack that Meld actually causes). If the user is the only currently
    alive Adept of the party members and uses Meld, the user will merely strike by itself and deal a Venus-based attack equal in power
    to the user\'s normal physical attack increased by 25%.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_19">When set, Meld increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Agility by 4, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_20">Steam</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_20">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_20">Increase all allies\' elemental strength</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_20">Aqua Rock</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_20">Steam is located in the interior portion of the Aqua Rock dungeon, placed at the end
    of one stretch below a moai statue that spouts flowing water that prevents you from running up to reach it. You need to acquire the
    dungeon\'s Parch Psynergy first. Then climb up the right ladder and go up until you\'re just to the right of the top of the moai
    statue, and cast Parch on it. The flowing water will disappear. Climb down and walk up to Steam\'s position and battle it in order
    to earn it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_20" formatted="false">When Steam is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts get
    buffed with an additional 40 resistance points to all their resistances.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_20">When set, Steam increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10 and base Attack by 5.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_21">Wheeze</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_21">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_21">Poison a foe as you strike</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_21">World Map, southwest of Tundaria Tower</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_21">Wheeze is a Djinni that is randomly encountered in a specific area of the
    overworld that otherwise appears to be pointless scenery. Thus, it is almost always missed by players playing the game the
    first time without any outside information. The battle with Wheeze may ensue in place of a random battle in the pictured area
    that is the southwest-most explorable area of the continent of Tundaria, directly southwest of Tundaria Tower.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_21" formatted="false">When Wheeze is used in battle, the user leaps forward to strongly
    strike the target, and a thick array of glowing purple images of strange, blobby ghostlike creatures is exuded upon impact.
    It deals a Jupiter-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 50 damage points
    added to the result, and there is then a chance that the target will be afflicted with Deadly Poison.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_21">When set, Wheeze increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base PP by 3, and base Attack by 5.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_22">Reflux</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_22">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_22">Counter an enemy\'s attack</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_22">Tundaria Tower</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_22">Reflux is found in Tundaria Tower, in a sliding-ice puzzle room you drop into.
    The room itself is reached when you get to a room with three stairwells going up; go up the center bottom stairwell and proceed
    to this room. Then from where you drop into, slide left, up, right, up, left, down, right, up, and right to bump into Reflux,
    then slide right so that you can then battle and acquire it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_22" formatted="false">When Reflux is used in battle, the user is affected for the entire
    turn by a unique effect which has the "always strikes first" property; the user does nothing for the rest of the turn unless
    the user sustains some form of damage from an enemy\'s action, in which case the user will automatically counter attack with a
    visual taking the form of a glowing red, ellipsoid portal of sorts briefly manifesting and a holographic image of a Mars Djinni
    shooting out to collide with the offender like a bullet. This counts as a Mars-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal
    physical attack.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_22">When set, Reflux increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Defense by 3, and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_23">Coal</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_23">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_23">Rally your allies to boost agility</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_23">Izumo, requires the Dancing Idol</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_23">Coal is acquired in a cutscene in Izumo. You first have to have completed the Gaia
    Rock dungeon, including defeating the Serpent, then triggered a lengthy story cutscene in Izumo with LadyUzume, Susa, and Kushinada.
    Following that, you may present the Dancing Idol key item that you had found and made use of in Gaia Rock to Uzume, and through
    another cutscene she exchanges Coal - a pet that has apparently become very dear to her - for the dancing doll of Mt. Mikage.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_23" formatted="false">When Coal is used in battle, all currently active and alive Adepts get
    their Agility ratings temporarily buffed to +100%, the maximum agility bonus possible. It doubles everyone\'s speed, in other words.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_23">When set, Coal increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11, base PP by 3, and base Agility by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_24">Haze</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_24">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_24">Hide away to avoid damage</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_24">Apoji Islands, requires Sand</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_24">Haze is located in Apojii Islands, in the right area that is the edge of Gaia Falls.
    To get to its position at a ledge hanging over the literal end of the world, you need to have acquired the Sand Psynergy earned at
    Gaia Rock. Then in the town area, walk right along the beach until you get to a series of rocks, and cast Sand to bypass the rocks.
    Cross over in to the next screen upon the shallow water, go down, and perform what might appear to be suicide - jumping down over
    the waterfall and off the edge of the world. You land on a small ledge directly below you, thankfully. Go upward into a small cave
    area, and cast Whirlwind on the third of four bushes; the entrance revealed directly leads you to the Djinni for you to collect.
    Go back to the cave area, and go out of the southeast exit and cast the Lash Psynergy on the coiled rope to let yourself back
    onto land.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_24" formatted="false">When Haze\'s battle effect is used, a unique illusory effect surrounds
    the targeted Adept, and the Adept is suddenly turned nearly invisible, represented only by a white outline of the target\'s normal
    combat pose in motion, while the game reports that the Adept "vanishes into thin air!". For the rest of this turn, the Adept cannot
    be affected by any action or damage against it by any enemy. This effect has the "always hits first" property which makes it the
    first used action in a given turn regardless of the user\'s agility, though if multiple units use similar increased-priority effects,
    the one with the higher agility goes first.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_24">When set, Haze increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base Defense by 2, base Agility by 3, and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_25">Rime</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_25">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_25">Seal a foe\'s Psynergy</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_25">Ancient Lemuria</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_25">Rime is found in Ancient Lemuria, the sublocation near the city of Lemuria reachable
    by the boat and the Grind Psynergy. It is hidden in the southwest-possible patch of grass that you can\'t even reach physically.
    Standing two tiles to the right of it, cast Cyclone, and Rime will suddenly appear and jump into the lone statue in the center of
    the screen. Then use the Tremor Psynergy while facing the now-shaking Statue to make Rime appear again, and you can now collect it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_25" formatted="false">When Rime is used in battle, a unique holographic visual of
    two intersecting blue symbols apply to the target, and the target\'s Psynergy is temporarily sealed. This effect applies
    with full accuracy compared to the Bind Psynergy that often misses.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_25">When set, Rime increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10 and base PP by 6.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_26">Core</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_26">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_26">Strike through an enemies defense</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_26">World Map, west of Contigo</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_26">Core is a Djinni that is randomly encountered in a specific area of the overworld
    that otherwise appears to be pointless scenery. Thus, it is very often missed by players playing the game the first time without
    any outside information. The battle with Core may ensue in place of a random battle in the pictured area in the center of the
    continent of Atteka, geographically west of Contigo and south of Jupiter Lighthouse but only reachable by docking on the west beach.
    It then must be defeated to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_26" formatted="false">When Core is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mars Djinni
    surrounds itself with a fully-3D special effect resembling a fiery sphere, and it pilots itself into the targeted enemy. The
    target is hit by a Mars-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 40 damage points
    added to the result. There is a chance that when the attack hits, only 50% of the target\'s current Defense rating is applied,
    sharply increasing Core\'s damage.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_26">When set, Core increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base Attack by 4, and base Defense by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_27">Salt</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_27">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_27">Restore allies\' status tu normal</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_27">Contigo</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_27">Salt is located in the town of Contigo, very near the bottom entrance. It is
    located just to the right of the entrance, in the exact center of a large patch of grass. Despite how easy it is to get when
    one knows it\'s there, players playing without any outside information very often miss this Djinni because the first instinct
    with grass groups like this is to use Cyclone to blow them away. As a matter of fact, Salt is automatically acquired by casting
    Scoop in the one bare spot in the center of the grass. Unlike other items specifically buried in the ground and findable with
    Scoop, however, the Reveal Psynergy will not even indicate Salt\'s presence in the ground with a telltale glowing spot.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_27" formatted="false">When Salt is used in battle, all status ailments from all current battling
    Adepts are removed, including the likes of haunt.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_27">When set, Salt increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base PP by 5, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_28">Petra</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_28">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_28">Turn a foe to stone</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_28">World Map, northeast of Shaman Village</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_28">Petra is a Djinni that is randomly encountered in a specific area of the overworld
    that otherwise appears to be pointless scenery. Thus, it is very often missed by players playing the game the first time without
    any outside information. The battle with Petra may ensue in place of a random battle in the pictured area in northeast Hesperia in
    a vertical "V"-shaped stretch of forest; this region is most easily reached by sailing the ship into the river opening on the
    northeastern tip of the landmass. Petra then must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_28" formatted="false">When Petra\'s battle effect is used, a holographic orange image of a
    Venus Djinni projects a stream of orange, gaseous energy at the target, causing the target to be "unable to move" for one of its
    actions this turn (meaning the enemy cannot attack at all this turn if it can only act once per turn, whereas a boss that can act
    twice a turn can only act once a turn). This acts first in battle regardless of the Agility ratings of the user and the target,
    and it shares its priority with other "acts first" moves.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_28">When set, Petra increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11 and base Defense by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_29">Tinder</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_29">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_29">Revive a downed ally</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_29">Hesperia Settlement</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_29">Tinder is located in Hesperia Settlement in the far western region of Hesperia.
    Cast Growth on the plant to the left, then at the top of the area where there is a wooden crate, push it off the left hole in the
    fence below. (Note that it is possible to push the crate off the right hole so that it drops onto Tinder and traps it, causing the
    box to shake similar to what can happen in Kibombo Mountains; you\'ll have to leave and reenter so that the puzzle resets itself if
    that happens, though.) From there, press the box right so that it falls further down, then use Move while standing below it to move
    it one step further right. You are now able to hop onto the top of the box and reach the series of wall ladders that connects to
    Tinder\'s ledge, as well as the cave on the opposite side containing a chest with 166 coins.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_29" formatted="false">When Tinder is used in battle, a targeted downed Adept is surrounded
    by a particularly elaborate visual of glowing red holographic images of avian pinions falling onto the target. The down Adept
    is revived and fully cured to maximum HP without any inaccuracy, just as though it is the Revive Psynergy without the PP cost.
    It is an upgraded version of Spark and similar reviving Djinn from the original Golden Sun.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_29">When set, Tinder increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12 and base PP by 5.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_30">Gel</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_30">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_30">Weaken a foe\'s attack</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_30">Kalt Island</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_30">Gel is located in Kalt Island, immediately visible as soon as you enter the
    location. To get to it, first enter the frozen river, slide left, down, right, up, left, up, right, up, left, up, right, up,
    left, down, and left. Climb up the ladder and cast Lash on the coiled rope, and you are led to Gel easily for collection.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_30" formatted="false">When Gel is used in battle, the user deals a Mercury-based attack equal
    in power to the user\'s normal physical attack increased by 50%. There is then a chance that the target\'s Attack rating is
    lowered by 25%. Note that attack-dropping effects may be stacked to a maximum of -50%.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_30">When set, Gel increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Attack by 5, and base Agility by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_31">Aroma</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_31">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_31">Restore eveveryone\'s PP</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_31">Shaman Village, after Trial Road</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_31">Aroma is located in Shaman Village. First of all, it can only be obtained after
    Trial Road is cleared because one of the buildings you need to go through is only unlocked for you then. After Trial Road, enter
    the cubic building built into the side of a rocky ledge to the lower right of the main town area, and come out of its top door
    and go right to the next screen. Position yourself below an earth pillar and cast Move to move it left one space so that it falls
    down to create a hoppable piece. Return to the main town, enter Moapa\'s house, exit out of the bottom door, cast Lash on the
    coiled rope, and the subsequent path will lead you to where you can hop across the earth pillar and claim Aroma.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_31" formatted="false">When Aroma is used in battle, a holographic image of a Jupiter Djinni
    surrounds the entire party in a sort of swirling purple, line-like energy, replenishing the PP meters of all current battling
    Adepts by 10% of their respective maximum PP meters.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_31">When set, Aroma increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11, base Agility by 3, and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_32">Whorl</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_32">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_32">Take a deep breath, and strike!</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_32">Jupiter Lighthouse</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_32">Whorl is located in Jupiter Lighthouse, specifically the right tower. In the
    room where it is located is a puzzle where you are to move pillars into holes in the ground to fill up tiles of floor to connect
    conduits for the Hover-based energy (similar to types of puzzles seen in Venus Lighthouse). Two such pillars are present,
    one a "corner" pillar and one a "line" pillar. Get up to the Corner Pillar with Hover, and move it over to the hole in the ground
    that the purple line of energy is feeding into, which causes the inactive hovering circle to the top center to be active. Use it
    to get to the line pillar, and move it off down to the ground level. Hover to the Poundable pillar to the other right and Pound it,
    ejecting the corner pillar from its slot in the ground. Now move the corner pillar to the lower left hole and the line pillar into
    the lower center hole, which will allow the lower left hovering tile to become active. Use that to hover to Whorl\'s position,
    save, and defeat it to acquire it. After that, simply use the lower left hovering tile to float to the upper left stairwell to
    progress to the next floor (you do not need to redirect energy flow again for the sake of activating the top left hovering tile).</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_32" formatted="false">When Whorl is used in battle, a holographic image of a Jupiter Djinni
    appears and sucks the target toward its position in midair for a moment using a reverse whirlwind of purple energy, before the
    target falls back down to the ground. It deals a Jupiter-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with
    an additional 40 damage points added to the result, provided its chance to instantly fell the target does not kick in.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_32">When set, Whorl increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Attack by 4, and base Defense by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_33">Shine</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_33">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_33">Dazzle foes and strike decisively</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_33">Contigo, requires Force</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_33">Shine is hiding in the upper left hollow tree stump in Contigo, and is brought out
    into the open via the Force Psynergy. The big potential snag to getting this Djinni is that the Orb of Force that provides the Force
    Psynergy in the first place is only acquirable as an item in the inventory of Isaac\'s party when they join Felix\'s party late in
    The Lost Age… provided any form of Password data transfer is in effect so as to register that the Orb of Force has been collected
    from the previous game\'s Fuchin Falls Cave to begin with. The Orb of Force can otherwise be missed, or not present in Isaac\'s
    party at all as a result of The Lost Age being played through without password data transfer at all; if the game file is saved
    after Isaac\'s party joins but the Orb of Force is not present, it will be impossible to acquire Shine without a hacking device.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_33" formatted="false">When Shine is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mars Djinni briefly
    backs up while emitting several beams of light at various angles, and then charges through the target. The target is hit by a
    Mars-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 60 damage points added to the result,
    and then for each enemy on the enemy side (not just the target) there is a chance it will be afflicted with Delusion.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_33">When set, Shine increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Attack by 3, base Defense by 3, and base Agility by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_34">Geode</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_34">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_34">Strike with a clod of earth</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_34">Atteka Inlet, requires Lift</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_34">Geode is hidden within the lower left part of Atteka Inlet where the boulder is, and
    to have it appear you need to cast the Cyclone Psynergy - but to get to it, you need the Lift Psynergy, which you only get as part
    of the inventory of Isaac\'s party when they join Felix\'s party late in The Lost Age. In Geode\'s case in particular, though, it
    can be acquired very shortly after the reunion takes place because the game\'s plot progression dictates you go from Contigo to
    Atteka Inlet right away. So, before going to the screen where your ship is, fetch Geode in the pictured area.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_34" formatted="false">When Geode is used in battle, the entire background suddenly rolls
    itself up into a 3D-sphere, and a holographic image of a Venus Djinni propels it into the target, where the sphere detonates
    in a humongous, 3D explosion before the background reappears. It deals a Venus-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal
    physical attack increased by 90% - the highest consistent damage multiplier of all Djinn, and much greater than the damage
    multipliers of its otherwise similar counterparts Flint and Echo.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_34">When set, Geode increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12 and base Attack by 6.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_35">Eddy</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_35">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_35">Speed up Djinn recovery time</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_35">Shaman Village Cave, requires Lift</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_35">Eddy is found in the main, large area of the Shaman Village Cave, where there
    are various boulders between elevated ledges that may be Lifted. The proper way to reach it is to first enter the room from the
    bottom end, then Lift the rightmost boulder. Go up, hop left, go down, and lift the boulder to the left of that. Return, then
    Lift the left most boulder, and cast Frost on the puddle. You may now hop to where Eddy is, and when it tries to escape it will
    be blocked by the second-to-right boulder. You must then battle it to acquire it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_35" formatted="false">When Eddy is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mercury Djinni
    floats above the party and causes arrays of bubbles to be absorbed into each Adept. It has the unique effect of instantly causing
    all of the current battling party members to go through one extra turn\'s worth of Djinn recovery time. The passing of a turn\'s
    worth of Djinn recovery time that transpires at the end of a given turn is unaffected, meaning that two Djinn in Recovery on each
    Adept will be re-Set this turn instead of just one when Eddy is used.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_35">When set, Eddy increases the Adept\'s base HP by 9, base Agility by 3, and base Luck by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_36">Gasp</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_36">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_36">Call the Grim Reaper on your foes</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_36">Trial Road, requires Hover and Lift</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_36">Gasp is located in the hidden area beyond the "goal line" screen of Trial Road.
    It is only accessible after Isaac\'s party joins Felix\'s late in The Lost Age because it requires both the Hover Psynergy earned
    upon completing the Trial Road contest and the Lift Psynergy Isaac\'s party brings with them. At the exterior screen of Trial Road
    where the battle with Moapa and the two Knights took place, cast Hover on the glowing purple Hover tile, then cast Lift on the
    boulder blocking the way to a secret area with lots of grass clumps and Gasp present. Along with looting the other aspects of the
    area, go to either the top or the bottom of the lower left lake so that the Djinni is opposite yourself, cast Reveal to show a
    platform in the center of the lake, and hop onto the platform to get Gasp pushed off to the side so that it can be engaged in
    battle to be earned.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_36" formatted="false">When Gasp is used in battle, a holographic image of a Jupiter Djinni
    hovers shortly above the enemy party as a mass of ghosty, skeletal imagery morphs and bends through the party\'s position. All
    enemies have a chance to be afflicted with the 7-turn Countdown condition. It is essentially the Curse Psynergy being cast on all
    enemies at once.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_36">When set, Gasp increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12 and base PP by 5.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_37">Fury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_37">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_37">Call forth wandering souls to attack</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_37">Magma Rock</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_37">Fury is found in the second, middle floor of Magma Rock, located to the far left of
    the lower horizontal hallway on an elevated platform. If you enter this hallway from the very tall black doorway to the right while
    the magma level is down, simply go left and climb up to where Fury is and battle it to attain it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_37" formatted="false">When Fury is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mars Djinni floats
    above the party and projects a wide, fast, and long wave of skull-faced orange spirits through the target, dealing a Mars-based
    attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 70 damage points added to the result. There is then
    a chance that the target will be afflicted with Haunt.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_37">When set, Fury increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12 and base PP by 4.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_38">Lull</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_38">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_38">Negotiate a temporary cease-fire</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_38">Loho, requires Magma Ball</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_38">Lull is present on one of the stone rooftops in Loho. It can only be accessible
    very late in The Lost Age because you need the Magma Ball collected at the end of the Magma Rock dungeon, which is itself only
    accessible after Isaac\'s party joins Felix\'s late in the game. When you have the Magma Ball, simply use it while standing behind
    the pointed cannon at the east end of town; after the wall it is pointed toward is removed and a cutscene transpires where the
    cannon is installed onto your ship, simply climb up the vine and go to the lower left, and hop onto where Lull is to collect it.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_38" formatted="false">When Lull is used in battle, a holographic effect of a Jupiter Djinni
    floats above the battlefield and projects an elaborate, swirling ring-shaped array of musical note images. The turn immediately
    ends; while all battle commands executed prior to Lull\'s usage this turn are unaffected, all of the battle commands that would have
    followed Lull\'s usage otherwise simply do not happen.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_38">When set, Lull increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11 and base PP by 6.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_39">Mold</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_39">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_39">Strike a foe</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_39">Prox</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_39">Mold is present in Prox, found near the end of the game. First, enter the frozen,
    snowed-upon river and go up to the next screen under a bridge. Mold will be right in front of you; when you bump into it on the
    sliding ice, it will adorably slide back and get buried underneath a pile of snow. Simply slide up to where the snow is and cast
    Scoop to acquire Mold.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_39" formatted="false">When Mold is used in battle, a holographic image of a Venus Djinni
    briefly absorbs itself into the target, then one of two things may happen; if there is at least one other enemy to the side of
    the target, the target will physically attack the other enemy (which other enemy it will hit is randomly chosen if there is more
    than one other enemy than the target of Mold) while the battle text reports "[Enemy] attacks an ally!", and the struck enemy takes
    the resultant damage. Otherwise, if Mold is used on a lone enemy, the target is suddenly damaged while the battle text reports
    "[Enemy], stop hitting yourself!". (The mechanics of Mold certainly make it a much different sort of attack than the in-game
    description of “Strike a foe” would indicate.) In either case, the enemy that is physically struck is struck with a Venus-based
    attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 80 damage points.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_39">When set, Mold increases the Adept\'s base HP by 8, base Attack by 4, base Agility by 2, and base Luck by 1.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_40">Balm</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_40">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_40">Revive all downed allies</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_40">Mars Lighthouse</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_40">Balm is located in Mars Lighthouse, in a large room with a slippery ice floor that
    you would have to go through on the first half of the dungeon on your way to the Flame Dragon boss battle. From where you enter
    the room, before stepping on the ice cast Move on the dragon statue to the immediate left and slide it to the left remotely. Then
    slide down, left, down, left, up, right, up, left, down, left, and down to place yourself just to the right of Balm. Battle it and
    earn it, then slide up to get to where you can get the Teleport Lapis.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_40" formatted="false">When Balm is used in battle, the entire party is surrounded by an elaborate
    visual of glowing blue holographic images of avian pinions falling down. Each of the downed Adepts in the current battling party has
    a 60% chance to be revived and cured to 60% of their respective maximum HP meters.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_40">When set, Balm increases the Adept\'s base HP by 13 and base PP by 4.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_41">Fugue</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_41">Mars</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_41">Fatigue your foes to drop their PP</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_41">Mars Lighthouse</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_41">Fugue is located in Mars Lighthouse, and is reachable only after Mars Lighthouse
    has been "turned on" and made hotter. From the "main lobby", enter the rightmost door, and you are led to Fugue pretty quickly.
    It must be battled in order to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_41" formatted="false">When Fugue is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mars Djinni
    floats above the party and projects a series of large, fast-moving glowing red symbols resembling musical notes in the enemy
    party\'s direction. Fugue damages the target\'s PP meters as though they were HP meters being damaged by a Mars Psynergy with
    a power rating of 19 and a range of All; if elemental strengths, weaknesses and resistances were not a part of the game,
    all enemies would lose about 19 PP, but the amount of PP-damage dealt will be raised if the user has a higher Mars power
    rating and the enemies have lower Mars resistance ratings. The amount of PP-damage will also be affected by other battle
    factors, such as being cut in half if the affected enemy is using the Defend command this turn.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_41">When set, Fugue increases the Adept\'s base HP by 11, base PP by 4, and base Defense by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_42">Gale</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_42">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_42">Blast enemies with a wind strike</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_42">Treasure Isle, requires Lift</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_42">Gale is located in the deeper, later part of the optional Treasure Isle dungeon
    that is accessible only with the Lift Psynergy that comes with Isaac\'s party when they join late in The Lost Age. Gale is in a
    particularly large room with several Lift-able boulders, presented as a puzzle just like the puzzle in Shaman Village Cave that
    rewards you with the Mercury Djinni Eddy. What is often not realized by players, though, is that Gale does not require to be
    "trapped" by a boulder that has been Lifted up (as pictured) because it will not try to get away via the space to its right even
    if the space is empty; all you need to do is to reach it and you will engage in the battle.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_42" formatted="false">When Gale is used in battle, a holographic image of a Jupiter Djinni
    appears and pushes the target away from the party using a projected whirlwind of purple energy extremely visually similar to that
    of Whorl. It deals a Jupiter-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 60 damage points
    added to the result, provided its chance to instantly remove the target from the battle does not kick in. When the target is
    removed from the battle, the battle text reports "[Enemy] was blown far away!", and if that was the only enemy in the battle,
    the battle immediately ends without any EXP or Coin rewards; otherwise, the enemy\'s sprite will instantly disappear, and the
    battle continues with the remaining enemies on the field. You will not get the EXP or Coin rewards from the enemy that was blown
    away, just for enemies that you actually fell.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_42">When set, Gale increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base Agility by 5, and base Luck by 3.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_43">Crystal</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_43">Venus</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_43">Restore HP to all allies</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_43">Yampi Desert Cave, requires Teleport</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_43">Crystal is findable in the optional dungeon Yampi Desert Cave, an optional endgame
    dungeon accessible only with the Teleport Psynergy. When you eventually get to its area, you will find a group of sand on the ground
    where something under the sand appears in four designated spots in a predetermined pattern and at a moderately fast rate. Find a
    place where it appears, and at the moment the moving sand appears in front of you, cast Scoop - you can use the Select button to
    open the Psynergy menu and take your time casting Scoop while the sand pile is frozen in place by the fact that your game\'s
    Psynergy menu is open. Crystal is automatically battled once it is unearthed.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_43" formatted="false">When Crystal is used in battle, an elaborate, circular glowing orange
    symbol appears under the party\'s feet and rotates counterclockwise as orange energy is projected upwards through the party. All
    current battling Adepts have their HP meters restored by 50% of their respective maximum HP meters, making it superior to the
    otherwise similar effect shared by the Venus Djinni Flower and the Mercury Djinni Spritz.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_43">When set, Crystal increases the Adept\'s base HP by 10, base PP by 5, and base Defense by 2.</string>

    <string name="lost_age_name_44">Serac</string>
    <string name="lost_age_element_44">Mercury</string>
    <string name="lost_age_flavor_44">Strike a chilling finishing blow</string>
    <string name="lost_age_location_44">Islet Cave, requires Teleport</string>
    <string name="lost_age_catching_description_44">Serac is found in the long series of hallways in the portion of Islet Cave
    accessibly only with theTeleport Psynergy found at the end of the game. It is hiding in an elevated statue in the second of
    the four narrow hallways, and can only be brought down to reachability by casting theTremor Psynergy while facing toward the
    statue. The Djinni must be battled to be acquired.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_battle_effect_44" formatted="false">When Serac is used in battle, a holographic image of a Mercury Djinni
    goes into the ground at the target\'s feet and disappears as a 3D polygonal iceberg appears at the position of the targeted enemy
    in its place and the camera swivels around towards the enemy side\'s perspective, and then the user leaps forward to attack and
    shatters the iceberg. It deals a Mercury-based attack equal in power to the user\'s normal physical attack with an additional 70
    damage points added to the result, provided its chance to instantly fell the target does not kick in.</string>
    <string name="lost_age_set_bonus_44">When set, Serac increases the Adept\'s base HP by 12 and base Attack by 3.</string>

    <!-- Djinn List -->
    <string name="title_activity_djinn_list">Djinn List</string>

    <!-- Djinn Detail -->
    <string name="title_activity_djinni_detail">Djinni Detail</string>
    <string name="djinni_detail_how_to_obtain">How to Obtain</string>
    <string name="djinni_detail_battle_effect">Battle Effect</string>
    <string name="djinni_detail_label_set_bonus">Set Bonus</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>
